<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Maintainerati</title>
    <link>https://maintainerati.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Maintainerati</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 18:42:07 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://maintainerati.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Not Alone! Sharing experiences at Maintainerati Berlin 2019</title>
      <link>https://maintainerati.org/blog/we-are-not-alone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 18:42:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maintainerati.org/blog/we-are-not-alone/</guid>
      <description>Visual notes by Carlo Gilmar
When I first co-organised a Maintainerati in Amsterdam in November 2017, I underestimated just how much my fellow maintainers need each other’s support. Meeting face-to-face is so important in building connections, friendships, and collaborations.
In my own personal case, I was drawn to run the event as I had one problem that I hoped to find answers to (refactoring a well used, five-year-old codebase) and I felt like I was alone, facing a problem I couldn’t believe was unique, but nonetheless seemed to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How You Can Help Build a Global Maintainerati Movement</title>
      <link>https://maintainerati.org/blog/how-you-can-help-build-a-global-maintainerati-movement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 13:25:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maintainerati.org/blog/how-you-can-help-build-a-global-maintainerati-movement/</guid>
      <description>Maintainerati events are pretty exciting. They’re a rare chance for leaders of all kinds of OSS projects to come together and discuss the many, many challenges they face running their communities.
The pain of conflict, the joy of collaboration, and the sheer difficulties of getting—and retaining—enough hands on deck are just some of the topics mulled over at Maintaineratis.
At the end of the day, attendees leave feeling full of ideas, with renewed enthusiasm for their work, and happy to be supported by their community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviving Maintainerati</title>
      <link>https://maintainerati.org/blog/reviving-maintainerati/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 14:09:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maintainerati.org/blog/reviving-maintainerati/</guid>
      <description>Maintainerati is a one-day Open Space unconference for open source maintainers.
February 2017 saw a group of open source maintainers gathered at GitHub’s HQ in San Francisco, an event then repeated in London and Amsterdam. Maintainers left these events feeling both inspired and empowered.
During these events, one important thing we learned is that maintainers need to have access to others who are sharing the same experiences, struggles and successes they have while running an open source project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>