<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maintainerati</title>
    <link>http://localhost:8273/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Maintainerati</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 14:26:32 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:8273/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Is This Thing On?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8273/blog/is-this-thing-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 14:26:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8273/blog/is-this-thing-on/</guid>
      <description>Howdy! This is just a mic check. Soon, the lights will dim and the show will start, but until then, we encourage you to check back in soon…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8273/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 21:25:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8273/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>(Adapted from the Open Source Feels Code of Conduct)
Short Version The Maintainerati is dedicated to a safe, inclusive, welcoming, and harassment-free conference experience for everyone.
All attendees, speakers, sponsors and volunteers at Maintainerati are required to abide by the code of conduct.
Need Help? Contact the organizers: coc@maintainerati.org or use the phone number found in the emails we send you.
NOTE: The coc@ email address currently goes to Jessie Frazelle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diversity Statement</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8273/diversity-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 21:25:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8273/diversity-statement/</guid>
      <description>(Adapted from the Open Source Feels Diversity Statement)
Platitudes are cheap. We&amp;rsquo;ve all heard conferences and communities say they&amp;rsquo;re committed to &amp;ldquo;diversity&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;tolerance&amp;rdquo; without ever getting specific, so here&amp;rsquo;s our stance on it:
We welcome you.
We welcome people of any gender identity or expression, race, ethnicity, size, nationality, sexual orientation, ability level, neurotype, religion, elder status, family structure, culture, subculture, political opinion, identity, and self-identification. We welcome activists, artists, bloggers, crafters, dilettantes, musicians, photographers, readers, writers, ordinary people, extraordinary people, and everyone in between.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>