<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maintainerati</title>
    <link>https://maintainerati.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Maintainerati</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 10:41:47 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://maintainerati.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Not Alone! Sharing experiences at Maintainerati Berlin 2019</title>
      <link>https://maintainerati.org/blog/we-are-not-alone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 18:42:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maintainerati.org/blog/we-are-not-alone/</guid>
      <description>Visual notes by Carlo Gilmar
When I first co-organised a Maintainerati in Amsterdam in November 2017, I underestimated just how much my fellow maintainers need each other’s support. Meeting face-to-face is so important in building connections, friendships, and collaborations.
In my own personal case, I was drawn to run the event as I had one problem that I hoped to find answers to (refactoring a well used, five-year-old codebase) and I felt like I was alone, facing a problem I couldn’t believe was unique, but nonetheless seemed to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Protection Policy</title>
      <link>https://maintainerati.org/data-protection-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 10:58:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maintainerati.org/data-protection-policy/</guid>
      <description>ol { list-style-type: lower-alpha; }  Last updated: 17 May 2019
Definitions Project means Mainterati, hosted by Open Collective Europe ASBL, a registered non-profit.
GDPR means the General Data Protection Regulation.
Responsible Person means Gawain Lynch.
Register of Systems means a register of all systems or contexts in which personal data is processed by the Project.
1. Data protection principles The Project is committed to processing data in accordance with its responsibilities under the GDPR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How You Can Help Build a Global Maintainerati Movement</title>
      <link>https://maintainerati.org/blog/how-you-can-help-build-a-global-maintainerati-movement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 13:25:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maintainerati.org/blog/how-you-can-help-build-a-global-maintainerati-movement/</guid>
      <description>Maintainerati events are pretty exciting. They’re a rare chance for leaders of all kinds of OSS projects to come together and discuss the many, many challenges they face running their communities.
The pain of conflict, the joy of collaboration, and the sheer difficulties of getting—and retaining—enough hands on deck are just some of the topics mulled over at Maintaineratis.
At the end of the day, attendees leave feeling full of ideas, with renewed enthusiasm for their work, and happy to be supported by their community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Core Team</title>
      <link>https://maintainerati.org/core-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 10:21:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maintainerati.org/core-team/</guid>
      <description>2019 Maintainerati Organizers Core Team     Name Contact Details     GitHub Don Goodman-Wilson don@maintainerati.org   Event Facilitation Gawain Lynch gawain@maintainerati.org   Knowledge Production Erin Taylor erin@maintainerati.org   Safety &amp;amp; Diversity Maintainerati Core Team coc@maintainerati.org    Regional Teams    Region Section Knowledge Production     North America - West Devon Zuegel    North America - East Henry Zhu    Western Europe, UK &amp;amp; Ireland Gawain Lynch Erin Taylor   Oceania Geoffrey Huntley Alexia Maddox    Team Profiles (Alphabetical by last name)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maintainerati Berlin 2019</title>
      <link>https://maintainerati.org/berlin-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 10:22:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maintainerati.org/berlin-2019/</guid>
      <description>Maintainerati Berlin 2019 was a one-day Open Space unconferencence for the community of open source maintainers to gather, present, and discuss the unique and pressing challenges they see in a face-to-face setting.
Now available! The Berlin 2019 Event Report and Session Notes:

The Event Report presents an analysis of 12 &amp;ldquo;Key Challenges and Lessons&amp;rdquo; that occurred repeatedly across the different sessions. For each one we describe what it is, what participants think causes it, and their ideas for how to solve it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviving Maintainerati</title>
      <link>https://maintainerati.org/blog/reviving-maintainerati/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 14:09:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maintainerati.org/blog/reviving-maintainerati/</guid>
      <description>Maintainerati is a one-day Open Space unconference for open source maintainers.
February 2017 saw a group of open source maintainers gathered at GitHub’s HQ in San Francisco, an event then repeated in London and Amsterdam. Maintainers left these events feeling both inspired and empowered.
During these events, one important thing we learned is that maintainers need to have access to others who are sharing the same experiences, struggles and successes they have while running an open source project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://maintainerati.org/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 21:25:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maintainerati.org/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>(Adapted from the Open Source Feels Code of Conduct)
Short Version The Maintainerati is dedicated to a safe, inclusive, welcoming, and harassment-free conference experience for everyone.
All attendees, speakers, sponsors and volunteers at Maintainerati are required to abide by the code of conduct.
Need Help? Contact the organizers: coc@maintainerati.org or use the phone number found in the emails we send you.
NOTE: The coc@ email address currently goes to the Core Team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diversity Statement</title>
      <link>https://maintainerati.org/diversity-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 21:25:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maintainerati.org/diversity-statement/</guid>
      <description>(Adapted from the Open Source Feels Diversity Statement)
Platitudes are cheap. We&#39;ve all heard conferences and communities say they&#39;re committed to &amp;ldquo;diversity&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;tolerance&amp;rdquo; without ever getting specific, so here&#39;s our stance on it:
We welcome you.
We welcome people of any gender identity or expression, race, ethnicity, size, nationality, sexual orientation, ability level, neurotype, religion, elder status, family structure, culture, subculture, political opinion, identity, and self-identification. We welcome activists, artists, bloggers, crafters, dilettantes, musicians, photographers, readers, writers, ordinary people, extraordinary people, and everyone in between.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>